What's up, guys? It's Matt, and today
I'm going to be teaching you the
official "Dai Dai Shakira" FIFA dance in
under a couple minutes. We're going to
do it really fast here. It's really fun,
really easy. You just have a big boom at
the beginning, and then you have one
more I like to kick, but you can do
whatever you want there. And then you're
going to hit a little 7 8. Hips just
hitting forward, you're saying, "Come
in, come here." First thing you're going
to do when this song drops, the beat
drops, you're going to go right [music]
and two and three and ha. So, my knees
are going out, I'm leaning down into the
right. That's really important. want to
be up here. That's going to be awkward.
You want to be down to the side. Hey,
two, three, other side, go hey, two,
three, and ha. Then we're going to chug,
step on that right foot, push, two,
three, four. Then you're going to grab
with your left hand, hey, six, seven,
eight. And again, my knees are going
out. Notice how I'm going down, leaning,
like putting a lot of style and attitude
in it. You don't want to keep this
straight up, right? So, here, hey, hey.
Then from here, really easy, I'm just
going to go one, two. So, I'm stepping
right, left. I'm going to hit three,
kind of body rolling up to knock, and
then I'm going to go a four and. So,
just hitting out, hips again, you can
add that for fun. And then you're going
to hit a little five, six, seven, eight.
Just grooving back, knees go out. That's
it. That's the whole dance. So, from the
top, we got boom, dot dot dot dot dot
and boom, six and seven, eight. You go
one, two, three, clap, other side. Hey,
seven, you chug, go push, two, three,
get low, five, six. Last part, you go
and one, two, [music] and three, four
and five, six, seven, eight. If you do
this dance, make sure you tag me, tag
Shakira. I can't wait to see your
videos, and subscribe for more tutorials
like this. I'll see you on the next one.